<?xml version="1.0"  encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><atom:link href="http://www.montrealzombiewalk.com/rss.xml" rel="self"type="application/rss+xml" /><title>Montreal Zombie Walk RSS News</title><link>http://www.montrealzombiewalk.com/rss.xml</link><description>Montreal Zombie Walk News</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2011 00:41:06 EDT</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2011 00:41:06 EDT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Makeup, costume and zombie links</title><description>Our links section is up and running!

You will find links that will be useful for October 22's Zombie Walk such as tutorials, video tutorials, tips for the costume and general links about zombies and how they behave.

More links to come, I still have a lot to filter before they are put online, IF YOU HAVE ANY especially good tutorials or links that you think belong here, send them to marco@montrealzombiewalk.com.

Thanks to Claire for the links!</description><link>http://www.montrealzombiewalk.com/en/news/Makeup-costume-and-zombie-links</link><guid>http://www.montrealzombiewalk.com/en/rss/Makeup-costume-and-zombie-links</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2011 22:04:47 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title>Liens pour le maquillage, les costumes et les zombies</title><description>Notre section liens est prête et fonctionnelle!

Vous y trouverez notamment des liens qui vous seront utiles pour la Marche des Zombies du 22 octobre, comme des tutoriels, des tutoriels vidéos, des trucs pour votre costume et autres liens généraux à propos des zombies et comment ils se comportent.

Plus de liens vont apparaître dans les jours suivants, j'en ai encore beaucoup à filtrer avant de les mettre en ligne, SI VOUS AVEZ des tutoriels que vous aimez particulièrement ou d'autres liens qui devraient être dans une des sections, envoyez-les à marco@montrealzombiewalk.com.

Merci à Claire pour les liens!</description><link>http://www.montrealzombiewalk.com/fr/news/Liens-pour-le-maquillage-les-costumes-et-les-zombies</link><guid>http://www.montrealzombiewalk.com/en/rss/Liens-pour-le-maquillage-les-costumes-et-les-zombies</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2011 22:04:47 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title>Montreal Zombie Walk at Infoman!</title><description>Last week, The Montreal Zombie Walk's team was interviews dressed as zombies for the talk show Infoman. During this interview you will see the organizer of SPASM's festival talk a little about the Zombie Walk then three of the organizers talking shit and saying stupid stuff dressed as zombies.
Thanks to the makeup artists Véronique St-Germain, Marie-Ève Tanguay and Deeva Gee!
So it's a rendez-vous this Thursday October 20th on SRC at 19:30, in the meantime you can see the interview's pictures here.</description><link>http://www.montrealzombiewalk.com/en/news/montreal-zombie-walk-at-infoman</link><guid>http://www.montrealzombiewalk.com/en/rss/montreal-zombie-walk-at-infoman</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2011 21:03:28 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title>La Marche des Zombies de Montréal à Infoman!</title><description>La semaine passée, l'équipe de la Marche des Zombies de Montréal a été interviewé déguisé en zombies lors de l'émission télévisée Infoman. Lors de cette capsule vous y verrez l'organisateur du festival SPASM parler un peu de la Marche des Zombies puis trois des organisateurs de la Marche raconter des conneries déguisés en zombies.
Merci aux maquilleuses Véronique St-Germain, Marie-Ève Tanguay et Deeva Gee!
C'est un rendez-vous à ne pas manquez ce jeudi  à la SRC à 19h30, d'ici là, vous pouvez voir les photos de l'interview ici.</description><link>http://www.montrealzombiewalk.com/fr/news/la-marche-des-zombies-de-montreal-a-infoman</link><guid>http://www.montrealzombiewalk.com/en/rss/la-marche-des-zombies-de-montreal-a-infoman</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2011 21:03:28 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title>Media section is out</title><description>The media section is now ready to receive its first medias. We only have a couple of goodies for now for but this will be filled with more pictures this week, then even more pictures of the walk and the zombie costume contest, along with videos and some footage from a movie maker.

More content will also appear on the website this week, tutorials and links to help you with your zombie costume.</description><link>http://www.montrealzombiewalk.com/en/news/Media-section-is-out</link><guid>http://www.montrealzombiewalk.com/en/rss/Media-section-is-out</guid><pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2011 22:18:55 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title>Section media en ligne</title><description>La section media est maintenant prête à reçevoir ses premiers médias. Il n'y en a que quelques-uns pour l'instant mais plus de photos seront déposées cette semaine, ensuite avec des photos de la marche et du concours de costume, accompagnés de vidéos et du matériel d'un réalisateur qui sera présent à la marche.

Plus de contenu également cette semaine, c'est-à-dire des liens et tutoriels pour vous aider avec votre costume de zombie.</description><link>http://www.montrealzombiewalk.com/fr/news/Section-media-en-ligne</link><guid>http://www.montrealzombiewalk.com/en/rss/Section-media-en-ligne</guid><pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2011 22:18:55 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title>Kitsch Halloween party!</title><description>One of our helpers is organizing a very interesting and unusual Halloween this year. Be sure to go check it out on October 28th:
https://www.facebook.com/event.php?eid=127987510634849
</description><link>http://www.montrealzombiewalk.com/en/news/kitsch-halloween-party</link><guid>http://www.montrealzombiewalk.com/en/rss/kitsch-halloween-party</guid><pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2011 21:26:42 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title>Kitsch à l'horreur !</title><description>Une de nos bénévoles organise un party d'Halloween plutôt hors de l'ordinaire cette année, alors soyez sûrs de passer
pour une soirée d'Halloween kitsch à l'os, mais jouissif à MORT!
https://www.facebook.com/event.php?eid=127987510634849
</description><link>http://www.montrealzombiewalk.com/fr/news/kitsch-a-l-horreur</link><guid>http://www.montrealzombiewalk.com/en/rss/kitsch-a-l-horreur</guid><pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2011 21:26:42 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title>Zombie Movie From Quebec!</title><description>The movie H5N1: PANDEMONIUM will be out soon! The maker of the movie will be there at the Zombie Walk of October 22nd to shoot some scences of all you guys before and during the walk that will be used in his movie. This is your chance to let out your zombie star!
Synopsis: Two brothers, former gangsters, sequest the owner of a drug-dealing bar that owes money to the brothers. The gangsters also take the customers as hostages, but a surprise awaits them. In this tense ambience, between the H5N1 virus and the zombies, will emerge an atmosphere charged with violence and carnage.
http://www.facebook.com/groups/86088227312/
http://www.stephanparent.com/h5n1
</description><link>http://www.montrealzombiewalk.com/en/news/Zombie-Movie-From-Quebec</link><guid>http://www.montrealzombiewalk.com/en/rss/Zombie-Movie-From-Quebec</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2011 23:14:41 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title>Film de zombies québecois!</title><description>Le film H5N1 : PANDEMONIUM sera prochainement sur vos écrans! Le réalisateur du film  sera présent à la Marche des Zombies du 22 octobre afin de prendre des clichés de vous tous avant et pendant la marche qui seront utilisés dans son film. C'est votre chance de faire votre vedette en zombie et passer à l'écran!
Synopsis : Deux anciens gangsters qui sont aussi des frères séquestrent un propriétaire de bar narco-trafiquant à cause d'une somme d'argent qu'il doit aux deux frères. Les deux gangsters prennent aussi en otage les clients du Bar, mais une surprise les attendent. Dans ce huis clos tendu, entre le virus H5N1 et les zombies, va s'installer un lourd climat de violence et d'hécatombe.
http://www.facebook.com/groups/86088227312/
http://www.stephanparent.com/h5n1
</description><link>http://www.montrealzombiewalk.com/fr/news/Film-de-zombies-qubecois</link><guid>http://www.montrealzombiewalk.com/en/rss/Film-de-zombies-qubecois</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2011 23:14:41 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title>First prize for costume contest</title><description>Here's the first prize for the costume contest that will take place at the Club Soda after the Walk on October 22nd (Value of $300):
  4 months membership &quot;Open Bar&quot; at Boîte Noire Mont-Royal, which gets you 3 free rentals per week.
  2012 DVD Guide, a collaboration between Boîte Noire, Mediafilm.ca and les Éditions Fides. Every year for the past 15 years, this guide the most complete reference of all movies available for rental, from the best classics to the newest success.
  A Boîte Noire bag
  A pair of Converse shoes, from X20-Rio 


</description><link>http://www.montrealzombiewalk.com/en/news/First-prize-for-costume-contest</link><guid>http://www.montrealzombiewalk.com/en/rss/First-prize-for-costume-contest</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2011 23:29:37 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title>Premier prix du concours de costume</title><description>Voici le premier prix pour le concours de costume qui aura lieu au Club Soda après la marche du 22 octobre (valeur de 300$):
  4 mois Abonnement &quot;Bar Ouvert&quot; à la boîte noire Mont-Royal, ce qui permet de louer gratuitement 3 films  par semaine.
  Guide DVD 2012 de la boîte noire, le guide DVD est le fruit d'une collaboration exceptionnelle entre la Boîte Noire, Mediafilm.ca et les Éditions Fides. Chaque année depuis 15 ans, le Guide constitue le répertoire le plus complet des films offerts en vente et en location, du plus grand classique au plus récent succès du 7e art.
  Un sac boîte noire, muni d'une courroie.
  Une paire de souliers converse, gracieuseté de X20-Rio 


</description><link>http://www.montrealzombiewalk.com/fr/news/Premier-prix-du-concours-de-costume</link><guid>http://www.montrealzombiewalk.com/en/rss/Premier-prix-du-concours-de-costume</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2011 23:29:37 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title>Second MZW Trailer</title><description>Here's the second Trailer of Montreal Zombie Walk, provided by SPASM festival. Thanks Jarrett!</description><link>http://www.montrealzombiewalk.com/en/news/Second-MZW-Trailer</link><guid>http://www.montrealzombiewalk.com/en/rss/Second-MZW-Trailer</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2011 22:01:11 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title>Deuxième Trailer MZW</title><description>Voici le deuxième trailer de la marche des zombies de Montréal, produit par le festival SPASM. Merci Jarrett!</description><link>http://www.montrealzombiewalk.com/fr/news/Deuxime-Trailer-MZW</link><guid>http://www.montrealzombiewalk.com/en/rss/Deuxime-Trailer-MZW</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2011 22:01:11 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title>Montreal Zombie Walk Trailer</title><description>It's finally there, the Montreal Zombie Walk Trailer by Nicolas Jehannin. 

Thanks to all the make-up artists, zombies, and all the rest of the staff who helped make this possible.</description><link>http://www.montrealzombiewalk.com/en/news/Montreal-Zombie-Walk-Trailer</link><guid>http://www.montrealzombiewalk.com/en/rss/Montreal-Zombie-Walk-Trailer</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2011 21:45:29 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title>Bande-annonce, Marches Des Zombies De Montréal</title><description>Le voilà enfin, le trailer de Montreal Zombie Walk par Nicolas Jehannin.

Merci à tous les maquilleuses (et maquilleur), aux zombies, ainsi qu'à tous les autres qui ont rendu ce petit projet possible.</description><link>http://www.montrealzombiewalk.com/fr/news/Bande-annonce-Marches-Des-Zombies-De-Montral</link><guid>http://www.montrealzombiewalk.com/en/rss/Bande-annonce-Marches-Des-Zombies-De-Montral</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2011 21:45:29 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title>A decade of SPASM</title><description>A DECADE OF SPASM!

You are all invited at the Club Soda this wednesday, October 5th for the official announcement of SPASM's 10th edition's program. On the menu: Trailers screening, distribution of programs and launching of the DVD: Under the Scares

And yes, the classic Dagwoods restaurant buffet will be there too!

Tickets and passports ($40) for the 2011 SPASM Festival will be available on site.

Open to all!

Doors - 17:00
Beginning of presentation - 18:00

Info:</description><link>http://www.montrealzombiewalk.com/en/news/A-decade-of-SPASM</link><guid>http://www.montrealzombiewalk.com/en/rss/A-decade-of-SPASM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2011 09:55:50 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title>Une décennie de SPASM</title><description>UNE DÉCENNIE DE SPASM!

Vous êtes tous invités au Club Soda le mercredi 5 octobre pour le grand dévoilement de la programmation de la 10e édition du Festival SPASM. Au menu de la soirée : projection de bandes annonces, distribution du nouveau programme et lancement du DVD Under the Scares. 

 Et oui, le classique buffet des restaurants Dagwoods y sera aussi!

Les billets et passeports (seulement 40$) pour le Festival SPASM 2011 seront en vente sur place.

 Ouvert à tous!

 Ouverture des portes – 17 h
 Début de la présentation – 18h

 Info:</description><link>http://www.montrealzombiewalk.com/fr/news/Une-dcennie-de-SPASM</link><guid>http://www.montrealzombiewalk.com/en/rss/Une-dcennie-de-SPASM</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2011 09:55:50 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title>The Web Welcomes Our Official Website</title><description>The organizers are proud to present the Official Montreal Zombie Walk Website.

While not all of the website's content is online yet, you will find answers to most of your questions. During the following weeks, more media, news, links, MZW-related events and infos to help you prepare for October 22nd's walk will appear.

T-shirts and stickers are now officially for sale. You can get these during one of our many following events that will be posted in the news section.


Finally, don't miss our official event launch this Friday September 23rd, 8pm at the Café Cléopâtre.</description><link>http://www.montrealzombiewalk.com/en/news/The-Web-Welcomes-Our-Official-Website</link><guid>http://www.montrealzombiewalk.com/en/rss/The-Web-Welcomes-Our-Official-Website</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2011 23:09:53 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title>Le Web Accueille Notre Site Web</title><description>Les organisateurs sont fiers de vous présenter le site Web officiel de Montreal Zombie Walk.

Bien que la totalité du contenu ne soit pas entièrement en ligne, vous y trouverez la plupart des réponses à vos questions. Aux fils des semaines, plus de médias, de nouvelles, de liens, d’événements reliés à MZW et infos pour mieux vous préparer à la marche du 22 octobre feront surface.

Des t-shirts et collants sont maintenant officiellement en vente. Vous pourrez vous les procurer lors d'un de nos événements prochains qui seront postés dans la section nouvelles.


Pour terminer, ne manquez pas ce vendredi 23 septembre, le lancement officiel du Montreal Zombie Walk au Café Cléopâtre à compter de 20h00.</description><link>http://www.montrealzombiewalk.com/fr/news/Le-Web-Accueille-Notre-Site-Web</link><guid>http://www.montrealzombiewalk.com/en/rss/Le-Web-Accueille-Notre-Site-Web</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2011 23:09:53 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title>Montreal Zombie Walk - Teaser 3/3</title><description>Third Teaser Trailer to give you a preview of the real trailer that will be shown the friday, September 23 at the Café Cléopâtre for the official Montreal Zombie Walk launch. </description><link>http://www.montrealzombiewalk.com/en/news/Montreal-Zombie-Walk-Teaser-33</link><guid>http://www.montrealzombiewalk.com/en/rss/Montreal-Zombie-Walk-Teaser-33</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2011 21:37:24 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title>Montreal Zombie Walk - Teaser 3/3</title><description>Troisième Teaser trailer pour donner un avant goût du véritable trailer qui sera publié ce vendredi 23 septembre au Café Cléopâtre lors du lancement officiel de Montreal Zombie Walk.</description><link>http://www.montrealzombiewalk.com/fr/news/Montreal-Zombie-Walk-Teaser-33</link><guid>http://www.montrealzombiewalk.com/en/rss/Montreal-Zombie-Walk-Teaser-33</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2011 21:37:24 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title>Montreal Zombie Walk - Teaser 2/3</title><description>Second Teaser Trailer to give you a preview of the real trailer that will be shown the friday, September 23 at the Café Cléopâtre for the official Montreal Zombie Walk launch.</description><link>http://www.montrealzombiewalk.com/en/news/Montreal-Zombie-Walk-Teaser-23</link><guid>http://www.montrealzombiewalk.com/en/rss/Montreal-Zombie-Walk-Teaser-23</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2011 21:44:05 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title>Montreal Zombie Walk - Teaser 2/3</title><description>Deuxième Teaser trailer pour donner un avant goût du véritable trailer qui sera publié ce vendredi 23 septembre au Café Cléopâtre lors du lancement officiel de Montreal Zombie Walk.</description><link>http://www.montrealzombiewalk.com/fr/news/Montreal-Zombie-Walk-Teaser-23</link><guid>http://www.montrealzombiewalk.com/en/rss/Montreal-Zombie-Walk-Teaser-23</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2011 21:44:05 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title>Montreal Zombie Walk - Teaser 1/3</title><description>First Teaser Trailer to give you a preview of the real trailer that will be shown the friday, September 23 at the Café Cléopâtre for the official Montreal Zombie Walk launch.</description><link>http://www.montrealzombiewalk.com/en/news/Montreal-Zombie-Walk-Teaser-13</link><guid>http://www.montrealzombiewalk.com/en/rss/Montreal-Zombie-Walk-Teaser-13</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2011 21:42:11 -0400</pubDate></item><item><title>Montreal Zombie Walk - Teaser 1/3</title><description>Premier Teaser trailer pour donner un avant goût du véritable trailer qui sera publié ce vendredi 23 septembre au Café Cléopâtre lors du lancement officiel de Montreal Zombie Walk.</description><link>http://www.montrealzombiewalk.com/fr/news/Montreal-Zombie-Walk-Teaser-13</link><guid>http://www.montrealzombiewalk.com/en/rss/Montreal-Zombie-Walk-Teaser-13</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2011 21:42:11 -0400</pubDate></item></channel></rss>